Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection
1971-2006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bernhardt, Debra E.
Baskin, Alex
Harris, Joseph
Kornblun, Joyce
Ramirez, Antonio
Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
OH.001
34.19 Linear Feet in 8 card boxes, 21 cassette boxes, 16 manuscript boxes, 12 CD boxes, and a half manuscript box.
5 Megabytes in 42 documents
New Yorkers at Work is an ongoing oral history project of New York University's Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives that seeks to document the history of labor and the working experiences of New Yorkers.
Access Restrictions
Repository permission is required for access to some items. Please contact the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was created by Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives with funding from the Rockefeller Foundation; additional materials were donated by Alex Baskin in 1997, Joseph Harris in 1991, Joyce Kornblun in 1982, Antonio Ramirez in 1996, and Louis Weinstock in 1981. The accession numbe associated with this collection is 1979.012.
Arrangement
The interviews are grouped into 1 series, arranged alphabetically by the name of the interviewee in finding aid. Access compact disks have been assigned numbers based on order of digitization.
Historical Note
Begun in 1979, The New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection is an ongoing series of interviews, conducted primarily by the staff of New York University's Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, that document the history of labor in the metropolitan area. The largest group of interviews were collected for the New Yorkers at Work: Oral Histories of Life, Labor, and Industry Curriculum Project. In 1980, with a grant from the New York Council for the Humanities, about 150 interviews were conducted with workers and union activists in industries representative of the city's economy. Eight documentary radio programs were produced from these interviews for broadcast over National Public Radio. Additional interviews were conducted by Archive staff to augment archival and manuscript collections; a few others were donated by researchers or students. The most extensive of these was a series of 15 interviews conducted by SUNY Old Westbury Labor Studies students of Professor Joe Harris—many of them with Long Island labor leaders.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access to some audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact NYU Special Collections (special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596) with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of oral history interviews broadly representative of 20th century New York City working conditions and union experiences. Topics include the impact of labor-saving construction techniques on the building trades; immigrant labor; CIO organization; the role of the Left in the labor movement and the impact of the expulsion of communist-dominated unions in 1949; public employee collective bargaining and the Fiscal Crisis of 1974-75; clerical organizing; new technology and its impact on printers and longshoremen; and the quest for economic opportunity by minorities and women. Please note the use of some interviews is restricted; transcripts or indexes exist for several of the tapes/CDs.
Notable interviewees include: Harry Avrutin, Brenda Berkman, Peter J. Brennan, Philip A. Carey, Charles Cogen, Edward J. Cleary, Sam Dolgoff, Ralph Fasanella, Abram Flaxer, Harry Fleischman, Philoine Fried, Dolores Huerta, Theodore Woodrow Kheel, Kitty Krupat, Josie McMillian, Joyce Miller, Pauline Newman, Lillian Roberts, Cleveland L. Robinson, Joe Stack, Leon Sverdlove, and Belle Zeller.
Labor unions and other organizations documented include: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; New York Joint Board; AFSCME; District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; Local no. 3 (New York, N.Y.), International Jewelry Workers Union; International Ladies' Garmet Workers' Union; International Longshoremen's Association; National Maritime Union of America; New York Hotel Trades Council; Newspaper Guild of New York; Social Service Employees Union; Local 371 (New York, N.Y.); United Automobile; Aircraft, and Vehicle Workers of America; District 65; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; United Federation of Teachers; United Office and Professional Workers of America; United Storeworkers (Organization); and Local 3 (New York, N.Y.).
Some oral history interviews in this collection do not have audio recordings and consist of paper transcripts only.
Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States.; Oral histories (literary works); Construction workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century.; Electric industry workers |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Merchant mariners |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clerks |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Hotels |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Clothing workers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Women employees -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Municipal officials and employees |z New York (State) |z New York |v Interviews.; Stevedores -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; Working class -- New York (State) -- New York -- Interviews.; United Storeworkers (Organization). Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. New York Joint Board; Avrutin, Harry; Stack, Joe -- Interviews.; Sverdlove, Leon -- Interviews.; Robinson, Cleveland L. (Cleveland Lowellyn), 1914-1995; Miller, Joyce -- Interviews.; Newman, Pauline.; Huerta, Dolores, 1930-; Fried, Philoine; Cleary, Edward J. (Edward John), 1906-; Dolgoff, Sam, 1902-1990 -- Interviews; Carey, Philip A.; Cogen, Charles, 1903- -- Interviews; Zeller, Belle, 1903-; Brennan, Peter J., 1918-1996; Berkman, Brenda -- Interviews; Fleischman, Harry -- Interviews; Flaxer, Abram, 1904- -- Interviews; Kheel, Theodore Woodrow -- Interviews; Fasanella, Ralph -- Interviews; Krupat, Kitty; McMillian, Josie -- Interviews.; Roberts, Lillian; United Federation of Teachers; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); United Office and Professional Workers of America; International Longshoremen's Association; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Farm Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. District 65; New York Hotel Trades Council; Social Service Employees Union; Newspaper Guild of New York; National Maritime Union of America; International Jewelry Workers Union; Communist Party of the United States of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local 3 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); Baskin, Alex; Harris, Joseph; Kornblun, Joyce; Ramirez, Antonio; Weinstock, Louis, 1903-1994
- Bernard and Marty Adelstein, undated; cuid264
  Scope and Contents
  Teamsters Local 813 and 1034.
  An electronic transcript is available.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-001 - OH-01-002)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-001 - OH-01-002, Box 31, Audiocassette 182A - 182B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 182A - 182B)
- Marge Albert, undated
  District 65, UAW; Clerical workers, organizing, 1970s.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 1A - 1P)
- Joseph Alissipi, April 15, 1990 and April 10, 1991
  Pennsylvania Mineworker.
  - Transcript, April 15, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Transcript, April 10, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-431 - OH-01-433)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-431 - OH-01-433, Box 32, Audiocassette 209A - 209C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 209A - 209C)
- Ernestine Allen, February 4, 1985; cuid45155
  Negro Actor's Guild.
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-003 - OH-01-004)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-003 - OH-01-004, Box 30, Audiocassette 162A - 162B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 162A - 162B)
- Tony Alleyne, September 21, 1981; cuid45062
  Taxi cab driver; Immigration, West Indian.
  - Index (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-005)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-005)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 2)
- Kathy Andrade, December 11, 1998 (Box 42, Audiocassette 251A - 251C)
- Sam Angel, January 3, 1980; cuid45063
  Paperworkers Union, Local 107; Immigration, Sephardic Jewish.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-196)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-196)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 3)
- Sylvia & George Aronov, December 12 - December 20, 1995
  Socialist Party and Garment Work.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-197 - OH-01-206)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-197 - OH-01-206)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 152A - 152E)
- Stanley Arnowitz, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Stanley Aslanian, July 11, 1984
  NY Lithographers and Photographic Engraves Union, Local 1.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-006)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-006, Box 29, Audiocassette 137)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 137)
- Larry Atkins, July 16, 1996; cuid45064
  BCT, Local 3.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Index (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-207)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-207, Box 33, Audiocassette 232A)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 232B)
- William Atkinson, June 26, 1981; cuid45065
  Department Store Workers, Local 1-S; Job discrimination.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-007 - OH-01-008)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-007 - OH-01-008)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 4)
- Harry Avrutin, July 7, 1981; cuid45066
  Bookkeepers, Stenographers and Accountants Union; Clerical workers organizing, 1930s.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-009)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-009, Box 22, Audiocassette 5)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 5)
- Irving Axelrod, September 18, 1980
  Painter.
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Index (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-010 - OH-01-011)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-010 - OH-01-011, Box 22, Audiocassette 6A - 6B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 6B)
- Roger Baldwin, 1971
  Clerical Worker.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-209)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-209)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 156A - 156C)
- Gilbert Banks, October 22, 1980
  Harlem fight back; Job discrimination, minority construction.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-210 - OH-01-211)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-210 - OH-01-211)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 7A - 7B)
- Frank Barbaro, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Harry Belkin, September 18, 1980; cuid45067
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-012 - OH-01-013)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-012 - OH-01-013)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 8A - 8B)
- Jim Bell, July 15, 1982; cuid45068
  District 65, United Auto Workers; Black Trade Unionist.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-014)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-014, Box 22, Audiocassette 9)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 9)
- Peter Bell, August 29, 1981; cuid45069
  International Longshoremen's Association; Technology.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-477 - OH-01-478)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-477 - OH-01-478)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 10A - 10B)
- Ronald and Peter Bell, August 29, 1981; cuid45148
  International Longshoremen's Association.
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-015 - OH-01-016)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-015 - OH-01-016)
  - Original Recordings (Box 22, Audiocassette 11A - 11B)
- Jane Benedict, December 6, 1983; cuid45070
  United Office Professional Workers; Clerical workers organizing 1930s.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-372)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-372, Box 23, Audiocassette 14)
  - Access Audiocassette (Box 35, Audiocassette 14)
- Julia Benicci, September 20, 1981; cuid45071
  International Ladies Garment Workers; Immigration, Italian.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-224 - OH-01-225)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-224 - OH-01-225, Box 22, Audiocassette 13)
  - Access Audiocassette (Box 35, Audiocassette 13)
- Robert Benson, April 15, 1991; cuid45149
  IBEW, Local 1381.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-017)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-017, Box 31, Audiocassette 193)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 193)
- Brenda Berkman, April 4, 1993 and March 1, 1995; cuid45072
  United Women Firefighters.
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-212 - OH-01-214)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-212 - OH-01-214, Box 32, Audiocassette 214A - 214C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 214A - 214C)
- Al Berknopf, May 6 and October 8, 1980; cuid45075
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-020 - OH-01-022)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-020 - OH-01-022)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 157A - 157B)
- Armando Betanses, July 23, 1996; cuid45076
  Hotel Trades Council, Local 6
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-018 - OH-01-019)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-018 - OH-01-019, Box 33, Audiocassette 233A - 233B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 233A - 233B)
- Howard Bethel, April 14, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Jack Bigel, July 30, 1987; cuid45150
  Harry Van Arsdale.
  Bigel did not consent to being recorded, so the transcript and audio present here are summaries of the interview provided by the interviewer.
  - Transcript of Interview Summary (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs--Interview Summary (Box 17, Cd OH-01-215)
  - Preservation Recordings--Interview Summary (Box 13, Cd OH-01-215, Box 23, Audiocassette 14A)
  - Access Audiocassettes--Interview Summary (Box 35, Audiocassette 14A)
- Ted Bleeker, March 6, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-352 - OH-01-354)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-352 - OH-01-354)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 154A - 154B)
- John Boer, February 6 and March 2, 1981
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-216 - OH-01-221)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-216 - OH-01-221)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 15A - 15C)
- Herbie Bostick, July 16, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Index (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-373 - OH-01-374)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-373 - OH-01-374, Box 33, Audiocassette 234A - 234B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 234A - 234B)
- August Brand, May 14, 1980; cuid45073
  Immigration, German; Furniture maker; Handwritten autobiography available.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-023 - OH-01-024)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-023 - OH-01-024, Box 23, Audiocassette 16A - 16B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 16A - 16B)
- Sara Bransford, April 12, 1990; cuid45074
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-025 - OH-01-027)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-025 - OH-01-027, Box 31, Audiocassette 180A - 180B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 180A - 180B)
- Peter Brennan, April 23, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Cassette 194A is missing as of Fall 2023.
- Gloria Broadhurst, undated; cuid45162
  United Federation of Teachers.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-370 - OH-01-371)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-370 - OH-01-371, Box 22, Audiocassette 12)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 12)
- George Brooks, April 18, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-028)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-028, Box 31, Audiocassette 195)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 195)
- May Brooks, December 13, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Thomas R. Brooks, October 20, 1991; cuid45159
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-029 - OH-01-030, Box 21, Cd OH-01-492)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-029 - OH-01-030, Box 32, Audiocassette 210A - 210B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 210A - 210B)
- Frank Brown, November 25 and December 9, 1980
  District 65, United Auto Workers.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-222 - OH-01-223)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 13, Cd OH-01-222 - OH-01-223)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 17A - 17B)
- Molly Brown, 1976
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-800, Box 31, Audiocassette 189)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 189)
- Roscoe Brown, December 22, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bernard Cacchione, June 30, 1980; cuid265
  Social Service Employers Union; Collective bargaining, social workers.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Index (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Notes (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 18)
- Lonnie Cacchione, undated
  Social Service Employers Union; NYC Fiscal Crisis, 1975.
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-233 - OH-01-234)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-233 - OH-01-234, Box 23, Audiocassette 19)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 19)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_1
- Joe Califf, April 24, 1994
  CPUSA.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-235 - OH-01-236)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Audio OH-01-235 - OH-01-236)
  - Original Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 219A - 219B)
- Angus Campbell, June 19, 1980; cuid45077
  Seafarer's International Union.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-031)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-031, Box 23, Audiocassette 20)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 20)
- Anthony Caprano, June 11, 1981; cuid45078
  Amalgamated Clothing Workers Union.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-032)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-032, Box 29, Audiocassette 144)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 144)
- Father Philip Carey, February 19 and March 6, 1981; cuid45079
  Xavier School of Industrial Relations.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Index (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-434 - OH-01-436)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-434, OH-01-436)
  - Original Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-434 - OH-01-436, Box 23, Audiocassette 21A - 21C)
- Elizabeth Smith Cassidy, December 6, 1996; cuid45080
  Hotel and Restaurant Workers, Local 6.
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Index (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-033 - OH-01-034)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-033 - OH-01-034, Box 33, Audiocassette 235A - 235B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 235A - 235B)
- Joseph E. Cavanagh, December 20, 1988
  - Transcript (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 181A - 181B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 181A - 181B)
- Frank Cedarwall, undated
  IWW.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-035 - OH-01-036)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-035 - OH-01-036, Box 30, Audiocassette 151A - 151B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 151A - 151B)
- May Chen, April 4, 2003; cuid45151
  Related Archival Materials
  Additional transcript of this interview can be found in the Asian Garment Workers in New York City Oral History Collection (OH 018).
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-237)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-237, Box 35, Audiocassette 259)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 259)
- Sam Cimaglia, November 17, 1990; cuid45081
  Cemetery Workers, Local 365.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-037 - OH-01-038)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-037 - OH-01-038)
  - Original Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 171A - 171B)
- George Cirkiel, May 20, 1980; cuid45082
  United Auto Workers, District 65.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-238)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-238, Box 23, Audiocassette 22)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 22)
- Ed Cleary, September 4, 1987
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 24A - 24B)
- Ed Cleary Sr., November 30, 1980
  International Brotherhood of Electrical Works. Local 3; Construction, NYC, 1920s-1950s
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Victor Clement, July 3, 1980
  Brick layer; Construction industry, 1890-1950.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-039 - OH-01-040)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-039, Box 9, Cd OH-01-040, Box 23, Audiocassette 25A - 25B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 25A - 25B)
- Cynthia Copeland Cochran, June 7, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-241)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-241, Box 33, Audiocassette 220)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 220)
- Charles Cogen, October 15, 1980; cuid45083
  United Federation of Teachers; Teacher's Guild.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Folder OH-01-239 - OH-01-240)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-239 - OH-01-240, Box 23, Audiocassette 26A, Box 24, Audiocassette 26A - 26B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 26A - 26B)